<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RealtimeProject</string>

    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="title_slide1">Connect the charger</string>
    <string name="desc_slide1">It will start automatically when charger is connected</string>
    <string name="title_slide2">Battery status update</string>
    <string name="desc_slide2">It will keep you updated on battery charging status through notification
    and home screen widget</string>
    <string name="title_slide3">Alert on 100%</string>
    <string name="desc_slide3">It will alert you when battery reaches 100%</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tourist_dashboard">TouristDashboard</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string-array name="island">
        <item>Luzon</item>
        <item>Visayas</item>
        <item>Mindanao</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="luzon">
        <item>Places</item>
        <item>Abra</item>
        <item>Albay</item>
        <item>Apayao</item>
        <item>Aurora</item>
        <item>Baguio</item>
        <item>Bataan</item>
        <item>Batanes</item>
        <item>Benguet</item>
        <item>Cagayan</item>
        <item>Camarines Norte</item>
        <item>Camarines Sur</item>
        <item>Cavite</item>
        <item>Catanduanes</item>
        <item>Ifugao</item>
        <item>Ilocos Norte</item>
        <item>Ilocos Sur</item>
        <item>Isabela</item>
        <item>Kalinga</item>
        <item>La Union</item>
        <item>Laguna</item>
        <item>Marinduque</item>
        <item>Masbate</item>
        <item>Nueva Ecija</item>
        <item>Nueva Vizcaya</item>
        <item>Occidental Mindoro</item>
        <item>Oriental Mindoro</item>
        <item>Palawan</item>
        <item>Pampanga</item>
        <item>Pangasinan</item>
        <item>Quezon</item>
        <item>Rizal</item>
        <item>Romblon</item>
        <item>Sorsogon</item>
        <item>Tarlac</item>
        <item>Zambales</item>
        <item>Metro Manila</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="visayas">
        <item>Places</item>
        <item>Aklan</item>
        <item>Antique</item>
        <item>Biliran</item>
        <item>Bohol</item>
        <item>Capiz</item>
        <item>Cebu</item>
        <item>Eastern Samar</item>
        <item>Guimaras</item>
        <item>Iloilo</item>
        <item>Leyte</item>
        <item>Negros Occidental</item>
        <item>Negros Oriental</item>
        <item>Northern Samar</item>
        <item>Siquijor</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="mindanao">
        <item>Places</item>
        <item>Agusan Del Norte</item>
        <item>Agusan Del Sur</item>
        <item>Basilan</item>
        <item>Bukidnon</item>
        <item>Camiguin</item>
        <item>Compostela Valley</item>
        <item>Cotabato</item>
        <item>Davao</item>
        <item>Dinagat Islands</item>
        <item>Lanao</item>
        <item>Maguindanao</item>
        <item>Misamis</item>
        <item>Sarangani</item>
        <item>Tawi Tawi</item>
        <item>Zamboanga</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="termsandcondition">
        TERMS AND CONDITIONS\n
1.	Introduction\n
        These Website Standard Terms and Conditions written on this webpage shall manage\n
        your use of this website. These Terms will be applied fully and affect to your use of this\n
        Website. By using this Website, you agreed to accept all terms and conditions written in\n
        here. You must not use this Website if you disagree with any of these Website Standard Terms and Conditions. \n\n
        Minors or people below 18 years old are not allowed to use this Website. \n
1.	Intellectual Property Rights
        Other than the content you own, under these Terms, Travelex and/or its licensors own \n
        all the intellectual property rights and materials contained in this Website. \n
        You are granted limited license only for purposes of viewing the material contained on this Website.
1.	Restrictions
You are specifically restricted from all of the following \n
•	publishing any Website material in any other media; \n
•	selling, sublicensing and/or otherwise commercializing any Website material; \n
•	publicly performing and/or showing any Website material; \n
•	using this Website in any way that is or may be damaging to this Website; \n
•	using this Website in any way that impacts user access to this Website; \n
•	using this Website contrary to applicable laws and regulations, or in any way
        may cause harm to the Website, or to any person or business entity; \n
•	engaging in any data mining, data harvesting, data extracting or any other \n
        similar activity in relation to this Website;\n
•	using this Website to engage in any advertising or marketing. \n
Certain areas of this Website are restricted from being access by you and Travelex may \n
        further restrict access by you to any areas of this Website, at any time, in absolute \n
        discretion. Any user ID and password you may have for this Website are confidential \n
        and you must maintain confidentiality as well.
1.	Your Content \n
In these Website Standard Terms and Conditions, “Your Content” shall mean any audio, \n
        video text, images or other material you choose to display on this Website. By \n
        displaying Your Content, you grant Travelex a non-exclusive, worldwide irrevocable,
        the application is not liable for any /n
        involvement of payment between a joiner or travel organizer, /n
        and if a tour or disagreement or cancellation of tours, the /n
        application will be not be apprehended by the law.

    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_organizer_profile">OrganizerProfile</string>
</resources>
